so two days ago I made
$345,000 in one single trade and I felt
nothing and I feel like I have to kind
of make this video to just tell you guys
the reality of myself and of reaching
this level of success so I'm going to
tell you guys some personal things so I
made
$345,000 in one single trade and
honestly there was days about you know
five six years ago where I would have
dreamt of this happening where I
literally also thought it was impossible
that it would happen this fast and as
I'm in profit in the trade you know I
kind of realized that I'm up multiple
six figures and I've been up multiple
six figures in the past but never this
much and I close the trade because the
trade hits my takeprofit as normal and I
go and I take a nap and I wake up from
the nap and my phone's blowing up my
friends my family everybody's kind of
congratul da me and I'm like what did I
do I didn't realize what I did then I
kind of assessed what I did and I pretty
much made very successful people's
salary in pretty much one single day and
that's kind of where I had a reality
check of like what's happened in the
last six years seven years of becoming a
successful Trader and successful
entrepreneur and how I've kind of grown
numb to pretty much everything I've
grown numb to the numbers I've grown
numb to the car cars to relationships to
just life as a whole because once you're
on the grind you kind of really want to
achieve this success right you want to
reach this status money power all of
these things and when you're in the
grind you kind of don't really see it
cuz you're in the grind right you're
trying to reach this goal and when you
reach the goal you don't really know if
you actually got there because no one's
going to come and tell you like hey
you're successful for hour hey you have
now reached the goal that you kind of
have to put that Trophy and that crown
on to yourself and kind of lately I I I
haven't put any crowns on myself I I
just kind of think it's my duty and I've
really normalized like who I become and
what I've done but this this trade was
almost like a reality check on the power
that I have Acquired and not not only
the skill set but like you guys you guys
watching this video like right now at
the recording of this video I have
300,000 subscribers like when the [__]
did that happen I just decided I mean
you know what I'm going to start
providing value on YouTube and I'm just
going to Simply help people out there
and grew to something this big and I
don't really think anything of it right
I just to me it just looks like numbers
on the screen it's not a really a big
deal because you know you always want to
keep grinding now that goes the million
but kind of when you have a reality
check like that it kind of makes you
realize what you've accomplished and I
got a reality check with you know you
guys that watch this video when the
other day I was I I was at the gas
station and I was putting gas and
somebody just came up to me and they're
like bro dude you have no idea how
you've helped me and changed my life and
I've get these things quite often I'm
like all right cool uh you know just
talked to him for a little bit then I
walked into Publix to do some groceries
and three people came up to me and then
later that night I go to the gym and
five people come up to me and I'm
driving back home from the gym and I'm
like what the [__] like what the [__] is
going on like I'm just getting my
knowledge and I'm just putting it out
here on YouTube and I'm helping people
and I I I don't I don't want to say I
felt weird but I almost felt responsible
for something right I don't know what to
do with that responsibility and kind of
how that got put on me kind of out of
nowhere right obviously you know I
wanted to put myself on social media but
I didn't really think it was going to
turn into this and you know you throw
into their the money you throw into
their like girls or relationships and
all that stuff and it's just like H what
the [__] is going on you know what I
mean because an average 23-year-old like
myself doesn't even have a tenth or even
1% of what I've been able to do so it's
kind of hard to decide what's my next
step it's kind of hard to if what I'm
going to do is right or wrong because I
can't ask my parents my my parents
aren't rich I can't ask my friends cuz
none of my friends are rich and I can't
ask anybody in my circle CU there's only
one person in my circle that kind of has
the same success for me but they think
very differently for me so everything
that I have to decide I'm deciding at
this point right now I'm like all right
do I do it for the better of myself
right now or do I do it for the better
of the people do I do it for the better
of something in the future and it's just
kind of very conf confusing on what the
[__] I do now because when you're in the
grind at the beginning to become
successful you don't think it's possible
you think that it's impossible to reach
success you think that it's impossible
to make $10,000 a month than $100k than
a million dollars a month
and as you're becoming more successful
you become more blind to the actual
success and become more numb to
everything because you're so deep into
the grind that you don't even realize
and it's crazy to think that all of this
started from Trading I came across
trading through a friend and you know I
got into this multi-level marketing and
the the lesson that I learned right at
the beginning was do not trust these
multi-level marketing Guys these guys
are not going to teach you trading
they're just there to get your money and
you know what I'm not mad about it
because if it would have not been for
them I probably wouldn't be in the
position that I am today who knows what
would be of Alex or set and forget or
everything that's been built
and thanks to that introduction into
trading originally that's where I
decided to now pursue this career or
pursue this business where it was a
pretty much Dark Lonely tunnel where I
didn't know when I was going to be
successful or not and I fa some really
really dark tunnels with my family with
my friends and with myself because you
just don't know when you're going to be
successful and I learned that by putting
your head down every single day and not
looking up or asking any questions when
is that light going to be at the end of
the tunnel if you do that long enough
there you would just simply pop up on
the other side and now you're at quote
unquote successful whether you want your
goal to be $11,000 5,000 10,000 I can
guarantee you the ability is out there
to do it I'm not the first clearly not
because I use other people as an example
so I can follow follow in order to reach
this success so when I was reaching my
first goals of you know $5,000 a month
so I can leave working at Dunkin Donuts
than $10,000 a month every level that I
got to felt like a stepping stone to the
next one I never really enjoyed the step
that I got to so let's say I wanted to
get to 5K as soon as I'm getting close
to 5K I'm already thinking of the next
goal which is 10K so when I hit the 5K
goal I never enjoyed it because I used
that as a stepping stone to get to the
10K and as I'm getting close to the 10K
I already set a goal for 20K and when I
got to the 10K I never enjoyed it I
never realized I never did anything with
it because I just used it as a stepping
stone for the 20K and I've been kind of
just running after go after go after go
after go without pretty much enjoying or
celebrating anything I've just been
chasing the next big thing and literally
yesterday or two days ago when I hit
this big trade it's when it hit me I'm
like holy [__] you wanted to make this a
year and you just did it in one single
day and this is one of the biggest
reality checks that I could have because
I'm kind of I'm kind of like I'm on a
treadmill just the treadmill just keeps
getting a little bit faster a little bit
faster a little bit faster and I'm just
getting stronger and stronger and
stronger but I'm not getting off the
treadmill at any point to enjoy the
strength that I have put on I haven't
been able to now run on the street and
you know enjoy the views or you know run
it to speed with other Runners I just
really haven't enjoyed any of it because
I'm just chasing that next goal and a
lesson that I can take from this and
hopefully you know you guys can learn
from it as well is when you reach that
goal and you reach that point enjoy it
because if you enjoy it if you're going
to get to that next one a lot faster and
when you get to the point where I am
which you definitely can the
opportunities are out there you can have
something to talk about when you get to
this point kind of right now at the
point that I am I don't really have much
to talk about other than you know some
fun crazy stuff that I've done but
they're this they're all backed by me
reaching this new goal that I want to
get there's no actual personal enjoyment
in it which kind of sucks but I feel
like I'm glad that I realized it now at
this age and this kind of takes me to
like my friends and stuff because in
order for you to reach these goals in
order for you to you know get these
stepping stones and kind of level up you
kind of have to leave people behind and
you might leave some real ones behind
you might leave some fake ones behind
but as you're running on that treadmill
you could only run on it alone you know
you could have some people in the
machine next to you and the treadmill to
the left of you or the right of you but
they'll probably get tired and they'll
probably just get off but you will be
the one that stays on that's why you get
stronger faster and bigger but maybe
that's not what you have to do maybe you
just have to get off for a little bit
and you go enjoy with your friends and
come back and I feel like I lost some
solid relationships with some people
because I was so focused on the grind I
was just on the treadmill and now at the
point where I am now it's very hard to
tell who's real and who's not who wants
me for who I am and who wants me for
what I have and it's kind of awkward to
hit those people back up where at the
point that I am now because it's like I
don't know if they [__] with me I don't
know if they you know what I mean it's
just a really weird position and it
could have all simply been fixed by some
simple balance by just getting off the
treadmill when the time is right and
staying on when you're supposed to and
as you start getting in these different
levels you know the point of making
money is to buy fun [__] or that's at
least the way how I see it you're
supposed to make money to buy fun and
cool stuff so you can go enjoy them and
I've always liked you know drifting
racing mudding all this stuff pretty
much all money did was get me funner
toys and get me bigger toys and more
toys so I can kind of go have fun with
it and I remember the first time I got
in a Lambo I was literally tripping out
I got in my Lambo for the first time and
the person that was driving the lambo
was treating it like a Toyota Corolla
and at that time I had a car that was
like a Toyota Corolla I'm like there's
no way like this is a goal of mine like
if I were to have this car I would
literally park it under a garage I would
clean it every day and
now I don't even realize that I'm
driving these super cars I have become
so numb to these cars that I kind of
lost the enjoyment of it I lost the
purpose of having a exotic car having a
super car because they've been so
normalized that there's nothing special
about it like I have a much better
experience when I let somebody else
enjoy it or when I take somebody in it
but there's not something that gets me
up every single day like like yes I'm
proud to be in this car it's it's just
become a standard part of my everyday
life and I feel like if I would have let
other people enjoy those experiences
with me or you know you know give back
to my parents or my family you know most
of these experiences it would be kind of
cool because you know maybe they can see
what I saw but now it's at the point
where I can be in a super crazy car and
it's not a big deal because I feel like
I rushed that success I rushed to get
this tangible asset like this and now
like I I just can't buy another car that
will make me excited like I almost like
didn't like enjoy the process of having
the car cuz as soon as I'd get the first
one I'd use it as a stepping stone to
get the next one so I never really
enjoyed the one that I had at that point
and it kind of sucks because kind of now
I've had pretty much every car so I
literally don't know what to get next um
probably going to I mean I got a boat so
the boat's kind of cool and I'm actually
liking that a lot
but I'm really getting bored of it you
know but I'm actually having a lot of
fun with it I say that's one of the main
things right now that is getting my mind
off of things and actually enjoying it
even though it's not a crazy expensive
boat I just have a generally good time
because I'm learning how to balance work
life and then enjoyment but I feel like
the one that really really like hit home
with me that it kind of still I don't
want to say confus me because I worked
for it but it's like the network of
people that I have I and literally one
person away from whoever you can think
of literally whoever you can think of I
about one to two phone calls away and I
didn't really realize it until when I
was in Vegas gambling with Dana White
Steve would do it Bradley Ana Ross NE
like all these big names and I remember
when I first bought my my first Richard
Mill I was like you know what I have to
buy that watch because one day I'm going
to be in the room with those guys and I
have to fit in I have to be that guy
that's at the same status with them so
I'm cool with them and you know I want
to just be their friends and I'm at the
point right now where I am literally
these guys friends not on accident but
just super non chalant like I can get
invited to a dinner just to go to the
gym with all these guys and there was a
point where this type of access to these
people was literally impossible it's not
easy I I didn't even I didn't even wrap
my head around how do I do it how do I
achieve it and it's at the point right
now where I can literally be one phone
call away from Trump and just pull up to
myo if I really want to and this was the
thing that put the final stamp on me
that you can do whatever you really want
like if you really really really really
want something you're going to do
whatever it takes in order to make it
happen now you can really really want to
do something but if you don't pursue it
every single day or if you don't put
thought or have know like a like a drive
for it it just simply won't happen and I
really wanted to just be cool with these
guys and one thing led to another and
now it's been the most normal part of my
life and it's turned into my new group
of friends and I can say that because of
the real person that I am and the
consistency that I have for my drive and
other successful people like that they
see that and they recognize it real
recognize real and that right there
would be one of the most simplest but
effective ways to show that you can
literally do anything guys I was like if
you would have seen me seven years ago I
was at Dunkin' Donuts I would have
literally asked you what kind of coffee
and donut you want now I'm at the point
where I can [__] buy the whole
Dunkin' Donuts all of that because I had
a vision and I was not going to let
anything get in my way to achieve my
goals and I get it I can probably see
that there might be some of you guys out
there that have limited beliefs and I'm
here to tell you that there's absolutely
nothing you can't do if you're watching
this video and you have the human
capacity that you're healthy you're
you're you're you're functional you can
do anything that you put your mind to
this is coming from a person that
literally had no resources other than a
winning mindset and a drive like there
was not one morning that I would not
wake up and work towards whatever goal I
had set for myself that day that week or
that month there was simply no days off
now that's a double-edged sword because
you can obviously reach the point of
success but you can get there by
yourself or if you don't get there by
yourself maybe you drag the wrong person
everything that you do it's going to
come with another end nothing is always
going to be picture perfect like if you
want to be able to be super successful
you're going to have to distance
yourself from your friends and your
family and it kind of sucks but you have
to ask yourself do I want success now or
do I want success in 10 years if you
want it in 10 years you can balance more
of your life it really just depends on
who you are and The Limited belief
should be the first thing that you
should remove off your mind because
there's
absolutely nothing that you can't do we
all have access to the same exact things
that I used in order to get what I have
today and the way how I get my [__] done
and I achieve everything that I want to
do I literally just write down what I
want to do let's say I want to meet
expers well where does this ex person
live who do they associate themselves
with what do we have in common
and i' literally do everything that that
person does I'd become a meanie of that
person I'd become obsessive with who
that person is and simply following
their tracks and then as soon as you get
to that point then whatever your goal is
with that person whether it's going to
be to uh offer them a type of business
offer or just become a friend or just be
in your circle you are doing whatever it
takes to get to that point if your goal
is to buy buy a car you set the goal of
the car and then whatever the cost is
whatever you have to do in order to make
that money and then you break it down in
time and task and every single day you
work towards that goal no matter what
circumstance and that's what I would do
every single day like I don't think you
guys understand right now it's 2 in the
morning as I'm recording this video
right now because this came to my mind
and there's nothing that's going to get
in my way to not transfer this video to
you guys and this week I want to catch
another trade so I'm going to Simply
stay up or wake up in the morning so I
can catch another tra like there's
nothing that's going to get in the way
of what I want to achieve and the
majority of the things that you need to
do in order to become successful is talk
to yourself because you're going to have
to go through some things that nobody is
going to [__] understand nobody is
going to be able to answer your question
so you literally need to look yourself
in the mirror and ask yourself is what
I'm doing right or is what I'm doing
wrong and you need to make a realistic
and a logical decision don't make a
decision to what's going to benefit you
in that moment or what's going to be the
easier route you need to make a decision
that is literally logical like if there
were to be a third person looking at the
situation and answering it for you so
they're not biased towards Pro or cons
and these decisions the only way you can
answer it is by yourself these decisions
will drive you to become successful or
not because there's going to sometimes
be some [__] that you don't want to do
trust me I have done so much [__] that I
don't want to do but I have to because
it's part of the plan and I have to do
to get where I want to get trust me I
did not want to lose thousands of
dollars in trading I did not want to
stress myself out I did not want to go
to work I did not want to work extra
hours but I needed to work these extra
hours to get more money to put into my
trading account I had to do what I had
to do I'm a grown ass man now because of
that cuz I take responsibility for what
has to get done because at the end of
the day the success is going to be for
the people that put in the time and put
in the effort do you think it'd be fair
that you right now watching this video
laying in the couch or laying on your
bed should have the same results that I
do I don't think it's fair because if
you were to go through everything that I
have gone through and you have the same
exact results that I Do by doing a tenth
of what I do it simply won't be fair and
the reality is that this world does not
work like this there's no such thing as
just flipping a switch and becoming
successful it does not work and I wasn't
this person that I am right now like I
became this person that I am now with
experience with losses with wins with
you know just life as a whole I was that
kid that used to smoke weed I was that
kid that used to run away and skip class
I didn't go to college I was that kid
but I knew that I don't want to be that
guy forever and I knew that there's
Endless Possibilities out there to
become successful because if there's
other people out there driving a superar
if there's other people out there living
in a mega mansion like what did that
person do what did they have to risk or
what did they have to work towards to
acquire that and if they were able to do
it why can't I like we're all human at
the end of the day we all have access to
the same things so what's holding me
back and what's holding me back is
myself the questions that I ask myself
the purpose that I have for myself and
the direction that I want to take for
myself and with all this you're going to
slowly find your purpose on why you do
all of this and I really didn't have one
to like the other day I was just kind of
just working to get more money and just
become more successful and have more
things but it gets to the point where
you just can't get more [__] like you
just can't and that's where you just
start finding a different reason to you
know wake up and work for all of these
things and the reason that I kind of
discovered that I would want is simply
just power like I want want to be able
to just have have the power to do
whatever the [__] I want and I don't
want to say it's almost like common
sense right but what what would be the
next thing that you would want if you
know a bunch of people already and you
have all of the things that you can have
tangibly family's good you have a family
you pretty much have all the free time
in the world what would be the next
thing that you'd want you'd want to be
able to do whatever you want however you
want whenever you want right and that
can come in many different types of
shapes and sizes and whatever however
you want to do it I guess mine would
just be to be able to meet other
extremely successful people I just want
to meet the most successful person in
China or I want to meet one of the Patel
families in India like I want to be able
just to be cool with these guys these
are legends these are people that are
pretty much making history and the only
way you can kind of get to that point is
by having this power and this power is
only for the better of everybody around
you because you're going to put people
in a position that they wouldn't have
been before maybe you go over there and
you know you just discover new things
and you know you get to meet other
people and you know other like-minded
people which are very hard to find when
you reach a certain point and if you
think about it every multi-millionaire
billionaire successful person in the
world everything they do comes down to
power like for example Elon Elon
literally got Twitter because he wanted
to create a platform that is unsensible
that you can pretty much do whatever
however whenever and the media goes
after him because you know they don't
like that that you know you can pretty
much expose whoever you want there and
nobody can tell you anything and he's
not going to censor what you post and
he's doing this because he's getting
power he's able to now put this type of
freedom for the people out there so him
having the power with all this money has
now changed the way people see the media
and they see things all around the world
power is for the better of everybody if
used correctly and I know this might be
like completely off topic what we were
saying but it just like came back to my
mind like the people that don't believe
in themselves is the main reason why I
want to make this video it's because I
want to show you that you can do
whatever the [__] you want you I have a
really really close friend of mine and
he's literally I only have two friends
through the through like literally the
whole entire process of me becoming
successful one of them has wealthy
family he's well and then the other one
doesn't no wealthy family uh you know
guy work construction towing cars
cleaning boats you can name it right
he's literally just like me grinding it
out to make money and I got into trading
and he didn't want to get into it
obviously I took off and then he stayed
in the same spot and he's seen me grow
month after month year after year and
he's been in the same spot month after
month year after year and we've always
stayed close we've always stayed in
contact and the other day he tells me
he's like bro I think I just got dealt
bad cards I think that I just don't have
luck or I think that I'm just not meant
to be
successful and I literally look at him
and I'm like dude with that [__]
mindset you're never going to be [__]
successful what difference do I have
than you have it's like well oh no you
you got into trading and like you just
put your head down every single day I'm
like so what what the [__] are you like
what's the difference between you and I
I put in the work bro and you did it and
that kind of like flip the switch in him
kind of realizing that he was just
complaining and making excuses and
that's what 99% of you guys out there do
you guys find the reason to put the
excuse on something else or somebody
else other than yourself and all that I
have to say for those kind of people is
just don't even try it just simply just
get a job and just work your 9 to5
you'll probably be happier than what I
am you probably have more purpose you
probably enjoy your more free time than
I have but don't get into the race don't
get into the challenge of wanting to be
super successful without getting ready
to get beat up without getting ready to
have endless sleepless nights and simply
without having to say a word and just
put your head down every single day
until you reach the success point that
you want to because if you're going to
take two steps and then look up and see
how far you've gotten that's not meant
for you like this is for you to take as
many steps as you can until you decide
you got to the point where you want to
get because as soon as I told him that
and I you know he kind of realized that
he was just literally making excuses he
started working doubles he started
putting in more time now he has
literally saved up money to now where he
has invested into a brand that he's
built where he pretty much you know
works with boat and you now he's like
you know has clients and stuff and
literally he texted me 4 days ago and he
was like bro I want to thank you for
that day you kind of just like put the
spark in me because I was making excuses
and I just simply didn't want to put in
the time because I didn't know if it was
going to pay out and it's like well
nobody knows if this shit's going to
[__] work out at the end of the day I
didn't [__] know I didn't know when
it was going to work out all I knew is
that if I kept going for long enough I
was going to hit that first goal and if
as soon as I got to that first goal I
was going to keep going a little bit
harder and I'd get to that second goal
and i' go a little bit harder I get to
that third goal like nobody knows when
this shit's going to work or if it's
going to work but all I know is if
somebody's already done it all I have to
do is follow those steps and just work a
little bit harder than them and I'll get
it a lot faster that literally cannot
get any simpler than that somebody's
already paved the way for you all you
have to do is just go put in the time
now when I see my friend again I'm going
to tell him what I just told you guys
right now at the beginning of this
video you're going to get to your first
goal and you're going to get to your
second goal and you're going to go to
your third goal and don't make the same
mistake that I did don't work towards
that next goal without even enjoying
that goal that you're having at that
point right there because you're just
going to get to the point where I have
kind of been feeling the last couple of
weeks and last couple of months where
it's like I don't want to say lost but
it's kind of like what the [__] is next
you know what I mean and with that it
would come a proper balance and then
you'd actually be able to now not only
grow faster but grow stronger and grow
more consistent and with more of a
purpose not just chasing a dollar amount
or just chasing something super tangible
that the high of you getting this will
go away really fast so if if you feel
something right now like if you feel
like this drive to go out there and be
successful just
like work towards something like you you
need to wake up every single day and
work towards something like what do you
do if you're not working towards
something without the proper balance
you're kind of just surviving you're
kind of just living you're kind of just
letting the time pass by for example for
my friend it's the boat stuff with my
other friend it's the animals for me
it's trading you have to figure out what
works for you because everybody has a
different ambition and a different Drive
I created an amazing passion for trading
and it got me to the point where I am
today so with all that being said I hope
this video was helpful so I've never
really disclosed kind of my personal
life or kind of like the way how I've
thought or I felt I don't know I just
don't really think you guys would care
um but if this kind of has helped you
and motivate you just hit the Subscribe
button you know it's super cool to know
that you guys actually like this kind of
stuff cuz I can you know remake it and
tell you guys a little bit deeper more
into the story and how I can give you
more tips to become successful so if you
guys liked it make sure to hit the
Subscribe
button and I'll see you guys in the next
one